# Luis Cano Irigoyen

### Objective

Computer Science student looking forward to working with growing and big companies, especially ones with job opportunities related to AI, game, app, or web development.

#### Relevant skills and tools

#### Languages

Spanish: Native

English: Professional working

proficiency

French: Elementary proficiency

#### Skills

- Data Analytics
- Digital Marketing
- Project Management
- Object Oriented Programming
- Market Research
- Search Engine Optimization
- Search Engine Marketing
- Writing
- Front-end and Back-end Development
- Game Development
- Web applications
- UI/UX
- Colaborative Projects

# Programming Languages and Tools

C++
C#

Google Ads WordPress GitHub

Unity

SQL Node.js / React.js HTML5

MATLAB Figma

CSS3

R

Python

Arduino IDE

Excel

Creative front-end and back-end developer with work experience in web development –making and designing sites for multiple companies and university groups–, in online marketing –being proficient in Search Engine Optimization and Search Engine Marketing–, and in app development –working with Unity to develop UI/UX layouts as well as game mechanics.

Experienced as well in teaching –having taught programming courses for younger students in two occasions.

### Education

#### BSc in Computer Science

— currently enrolled

Tecnológico de Monterrey Monterrey, Nuevo León, México

Expected Graduation year: 2023

#### International Baccalaureate Diploma

Liceo de Monterrey Centro Educativo Monterrey, Nuevo León, México

Graduation year: 2019

## Experience

#### Digital Analyst

Forte Industria & Cocina del Chef // May 2021 – Present

 I currently work as a Digital Analyst, Web Developer and SEO Analyst at Forte Industria —an online retailer of industrial machinery— and at Cocina del Chef —an online retailer of kitchen related products.

#### Unity Developer Internship

<u>Gamejam</u> // Jun 2021 - Aug 2021

- Implemented UI/UX layouts from Figma into a now published Unity Game.
- Developed an idea/brief into a game prototype, creating: Player mechanics, Enemies AI, Obstacles and interactions with them, Editor Tool for Level Building.
- Worked with a large team providing ideas for others and implementing received feedback into my own projects.

#### Web Developer & Marketing Analyst

Pixelwork Agencia Web // Jul 2019 - Apr 2021

- Utilized WordPress for building company websites.
- Worked with Ahrefs and Yoast to and increase with success the organic traffic value of multiple domains, as well as making their websites healthier.
- o Created and Managed multiple Google Ads campaigns.

### Contact information

Email:

Find me at:

lcanoi0510@gmail.com

Website Linkedli

Phone: 81 2349 2066

GitHub